Guide to the Walter F. W. Lohnes Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-041
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 1966 (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - W.W. Norton reviews of Lohnes-Strothmann, 1985 (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Teacher's Manual for the 4th edition of Lohnes-Strothmann (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Corrections to Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition (+correspondence from W.W. Norton) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Preface, Intro., Sounds of German (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 5 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 6 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 7 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 8 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 9 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 10 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 11 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 12 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 13 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 14 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 15 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 16 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 17 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann, 4th edition - Unit 18 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - W.W. Norton - reviews, comments, and correspondence on Lohnes-Strothmann (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Material for Teacher's Manual (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Teacher's Manual for German: A Structural Approach, shorter edition (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Student's Laboratory Manual for German: A Structural Approach, shorter edition (+correspondence) (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann - drafts of the preface, intro., and Sounds of German (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lohnes-Strothmann - tape exercise times and table of contents (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, esp. with W.W. Norton and regarding Lohnes and Strothmann (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Preface and Intro., and correspondence with W.W. Norton (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - A Teacher's Manual for German: A Structural Approach (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - "The German, Austrian, and Swiss Chairs at Stanford: A Historical Note" by Walter F.W. Lohnes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Germany, summer 1976 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - German and Austrian Chairs, 1976 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bericht - Prof. Dr. M. Rainer Lepsius, Mannheim, May 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - German Chair Proposal - Schlenzka(?) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - German and Austrian Chairs, 1977 (1) (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - German and Austrian Chairs, Berlin - Mar. 1977-May 1977 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Austrian and German Chairs, Berlin Program - June 1977-Dec. 1977 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Austrian and German Chairs, Berlin - Jan. 1978-July 1979 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Holiday Inn reservations for the Swiss Symposium, Mar. 1-3, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Brochures for the Swiss Symposium, Mar. 1-3, 1991 - "Switzerland in a Changing World" (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Swiss Symposium - correspondence (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mailing lists (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Alumni in Switzerland (lists) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Swiss Symposium - Curriculum Vitae (C.V.'s) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Swiss Symposium - finances (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Swiss Symposium - Plattner (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Swiss Symposium - follow-up correspondence (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Pro Helvetia (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Swiss Travel Arrangements (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Swiss Symposium - papers (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Swiss Symposium - program (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Swiss Festival, 1991 - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Swiss Chair - miscellaneous and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Swiss Chair, 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Swiss Chair proposal (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - German Chair (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Swiss Chair, 1989-90 (+correspondence) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Prof. Maurice Jaccard - papers, exams, and correspondence (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NEH (National Endowment for the Humanities) application, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NEH application, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - IBG (Institute for Basic German)--DARE (Dictionary of American Regional English); Frederic Cassidy, Auntie Blue (+correspondence and article) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - IBG (Institute for Basic German) proposal, 1977 (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - IBG - correspondence and miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - IBG cost overrun (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NEH (National Endowment for the Humanities) renewal, 1980-82 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NEH application, 1985; IBG (Institute for Basic German) (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NEH grant - Frequency and Range Dictionaries (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1982 proposal - extra copies (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NEH grant (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NEH proposal (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NEH Interim Report, Dec. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Auntie Blue proposal (NEH), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NEH renewal proposal, Dec. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NEH DARE (Dictionary of American Regional English) proposal, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - NEH proposal, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - "Editing, Formatting, and Computer Processing of the Data" (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - IBG (Institute for Basic German) I - introduction for book version (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - IBG orders (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Kettemann, Bernhard - papers and correspondence (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous German papers (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - IBG - Level 1, printouts, etc. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - IBG - German Corpora (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - IBG - European Corpora (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - IBG - Rosengren Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - IBG - Mannheim/Ost-West (+correspondence) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - IBG - Inst. Deutsche Sprache Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - IBG - AILA (?) Bulletin, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - IBG - Goethe-Inst. Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - IBG Correspondence with J.A. Pfeffer (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Binders:
    - Trips, 1967 - Plane-bus-car; Berlin; Cologne; Area studies; Tests; Materials; Concerts, etc. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Institute Financial - miscellaneous, correspondence, and records (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - OE (Office of Education), 1967 - "Confidential" - Financial-Stanford; OE Instructions; Manuals; Plan of Operation; Contract; Corresp. with other institutes (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Trips, 1968 - Plane-bus-car; Berlin; Cologne; Area studies; tests; materials; concerts, etc. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Participants-staff, 1968 - miscellaneous, correspondence, and records (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Institute, 1967 - miscellaneous, correspondence, and records (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-117
  - ACTFL Anaheim ‘95 Nov. 17-20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GSA - Chicago 1995 Sep. 20-24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AATG - Atlanta ‘94 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - MLA ‘93 - Toronto (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - San Antonio Nov. ‘93 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Leipzig Aug. ‘93 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vienna/Strobl 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AATG ‘89 - Boston (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Consortium - Phila, Oct. ‘89 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - MLA - ‘88 - New Orleans (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AATG - Monterey Nov. ‘88 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hagens/Princeton July ‘88 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Apr. ‘88 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - MLA 1987 - SFO (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ADFL - West BYU June ‘87 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - W.W. Norton 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AATG - Nov. ‘92 - Chicago (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AATG/ACTFL Wash. ‘91 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Consortium Meeting - Yale Apr. ‘91 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AATG Nashville ‘90 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Media Services Advisory Committee 1989 - (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AP Committee (ad hoc) 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Scanner Committee (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - German Univ. - Ranking (Spiegel) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lang. Lab. Committee (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lang. Lab. Committee 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - DDR (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Herder Institut - Leipzig (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Herder-Institut Nov. ‘89 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Welzig Paper (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Vienna Center Fundraising (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Vienna Closure (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Topics for Master's Theses (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reading Lists - Ph. D. Orals (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Question, for Ph.D. Exams (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Strengthening the Humanities Through Foreign Language and Literature Studies (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Story of Hapless Henry (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rede von Hans Christoph Freiherr von Stauffenberg am 2. August 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mental Representations and Language in Action (1) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Die Vaskische Haupt-und Muttersprache (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - C + D and L. D. ‘91-'92 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - German 52: Readings in Poli Sci and IR; Fall 1986/87 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 11P (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - L.D. ‘95 -'96 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - C + D/Lower Div. ‘94/95 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - L. D. ‘94 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - L. D. ‘93 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Oral History Project (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Madison Conference April ‘83 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Video - Project 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - MLA ‘82 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Textbook authors conference G.I. Chicago, April 16-17, ‘82 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MLA 1981 - NYC (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Taos (UNM) 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - MLA - Houston 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Poznan Conference Dec. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - U of New Mexico Summer 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Grant applications for ‘80/81 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - GSUS Section MLA 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - AATG - Asilomar Nov. 9-11, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Reschke Project (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - NEH Seminar Application 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - IREX 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - MLA 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Monterey Institute, Feb. ‘86 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - GSA - Washington D.C. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - German Studies Symposium Taos, July ‘85 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MLA 1984 - Wash. D.C. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Vienna 1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - New Mexico 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - GSA - Albuquerque 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ph. D. List (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Eric Wilson Opera (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ph. D. letters 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ph. D. lists ‘89 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - letter to Ph. D.s - March 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Department Faculty List 1960 - (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Department History (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dept & Nat'l Statistics (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Departments and Courses of Instruction (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - School of Humanities/Germanic Languages (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1909 -1918 (copies of William A. Cooper's correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1917 - 1936 (copies of William A. Cooper's correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1917 - 1938 (copies of William A. Cooper's correspondence) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Consortium - CTL (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Zertificat Deutsch aF + Grosses Sprachdiplom (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bonn (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Proficiency (1985) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Oral Prof. Interviews June 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Industrie Kulter Exhibit (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Western European Studies German Advisory Committee (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Search ‘93/94 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Search ‘93 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - GRE meeting - Princeton April 10 -13,'75 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - N.E. Conf. - April 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Madison Trip (ADFL) June ‘75 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - MLA - San Francisco, 12/26 - 29, ‘75 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Grants - ‘76 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Grants 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller Application for 1976-77 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim aplication 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1974/75 WFWL ACLS Appl. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1974 + 1979 WFWL NEH Appl. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - AATG Meeting 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - MLA ‘77 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - AATG meet. ‘78 Chicago (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - MLA--December 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - WFWL - C + D 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - WFWL - GB/C + D (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Syllabi + Exams ‘91-92 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Crunch (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Library (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Centr. Eur. Studies - Proposal 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CRIS Advisory Committee 1975-76 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - John Flores (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NEH Summer Seminar Proposal 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MLA 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1976 - AATG Symposium (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Student Papers (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - G 205 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Fruhwirt - Austrian Advisory Committee (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Austrian Chair 1990 - (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Austr. Chair + Conferences (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Austrian Chair letter to chairmen (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Visiting Prof. for Austrian Studies 1978 - 1990 A-Z (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Visiting Prof. for Austrian Studies The Committee 1981 - (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Visiting Prof. for Austrian Studies CRIS/IIS (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Visiting Prof. for Austrian Studies Chairs generally, Institutes, Centers, Departments (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Werkner ‘89/90 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Wendelin Schmidt-Dengler ‘90/91 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Peter Posch 1991-92 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ruth Wodak 1992/93 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kralj, Matthias - Drama (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Schleicher, Conf. March ‘95 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Schleicher (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Gerhard Hafner (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Visiting Prof. for Austrian Studies 1990/91 - and candidates A-Z (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Schiele - Symposium 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Mozart Colloquium May ‘91 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Austrian Center Proposal 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Austrian Alumni Club 1990 - (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Austria ‘89/90 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Austr. Chair (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Teaching Evaluation Reports (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations A-G (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations H-P (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Recommendaitons Q-Z (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Class Visits (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1996-132
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - College Board Advanced Placement German Testing (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AUDIO TAPES - Lohnes and Strothman. German: A Structural Approach
    - Unit 1, Reels 1,2,3 (Box 3)
    - Unit 2, Reels 1,3,4 (Box 3)
    - Unit 3, Reels 1,2,3,4,5 (Box 3)
    - Unit 4, Reels 1,2,3 (Box 3)
    - Unit 4, Reels 4,5,6 (Box 4)
    - Unit 5, Reels 1,2,3,4,5 (Box 4)
    - Unit 6, Reels 1,2,3,4,5,6 (Box 4)
    - Unit 7, Reels 4,5 (Box 5)
    - Unit 8, Reels 1,2,3,4,5,6 (Box 5)
    - Unit 9, Reels 2,3,4,5 (Box 5)
    - Unit 10, Reels 1,2 (Box 5)
    - Unit 10, Reels 3,4,5,6 (Box 6)
    - Unit 11, Reels 1,2,4 (Box 6)
    - Unit 12, Reels 1,2,3,4,5 (Box 6)
    - Unit 13, Reels 3,4,5 (Box 6)
    - Unit PRON, Reels 1,2,3,5 (Box 7)
    - Unit 1, Reel 1 (1.1 - 1.7) (Box 7)
    - Unit 1, Reel 2 (1.8 - 1.12) (Box 7)
    - Unit 2, Reel 1 (2.1 - 2.8) (Box 7)
    - Unit 3, Reel 1 (3.1 - 3.7) (Box 7)
    - Unit 3, Reel 2 (3.8 - 3.15) (Box 7)
    - Unit 4, Reel 1 (4.1 - 4.7) (Box 7)
    - Unit 4, Reel 2 (4.8 - 4.10) (Box 7)
    - Unit 5, Reel 1 (5.1 - 5.5) (Box 7)
    - Unit 5, Reel 2 (5.6 - 5.12) (Box 7)
    - Unit 6, Reel 1 (6.1 - 6.11) (Box 7)
    - Unit 6, Reel 2 (6.12 - 6.15) (Box 8)
    - Unit 7, Reel 1 (7.1 - 7.6) (Box 8)
    - Unit 7, Reel 2 (7.6 - 7.9) (Box 8)
    - Unit 8, Reel 1 (8.1 -8.7) (Box 8)
    - Unit 8, Reel 2 (8.8 - 8.14)) (Box 8)
    - Unit 9, Reel 1 (9.1 - 9.6) (Box 8)
    - Unit 9, Reel 2 (9.7 - 9.12) (Box 8)
    - Unit 10, Reel 1 (10.1 - 10.7) (Box 8)
    - Unit 10, Reel 2 (10.8 - 10.9) (Box 8)
    - Unit 11, Reel 1 (11.1 - 11.6) (Box 8)
    - Unit 11, Reel 2 (11.7-11.11) (Box 8)
    - Unit 12, Reel 1 (12.1 - 12.6) (Box 8)
    - Unit 12, Reel 2 (12.7 - 12.9) (Box 8)
    - Unit 13, Reel 1 (13.1 - 13.6) (Box 8)
    - Unit 13, Reel 2 (13.7-13.10) (Box 9)
  - The Second Year: Side A, tape 1; Side B, tape 2
    Third Edition:
    - Reel 1, Side A, Unit 1 (Box 9)
    - Reel 1, Side B, Unit 2 (Box 9)
    - Reel 2, Side A, Unit 3 (Box 9)
    - Reel 2, Side B, Unit 4 (Box 9)
    - Reel 3, Side A, Unit 5 (Box 9)
    - Reel 3, Side B, Unit 6 (Box 9)
    - Reel 4, Side A, Unit 7 (Box 9)
    - Reel 4, Side B, Unit 8 (Box 9)
    - Reel 5, Side A, Unit 9 (Box 9)
    - Reel 5, Side B, Unit 10 (Box 9)
    - Reel 6, Side A, Unit 11 (Box 9)
    - Reel 6, Side B, Unit 12 (Box 9)
    - Reel 7, Side A, Unit 13 (Box 9)
    - Reel 7, Side B, Unit 14 (Box 9)
    - Reel 8, Side A, Unit 15 (Box 9)
    - Reel 8, Side B, Unit 16 (Box 9)
    - Reel 9, Side A, Unit 17 (Box 9)
    - Reel 9, Side B, Unit 18 (Box 9)
  - Shorter Edition Tape Proof Only
    Modified Version Proof Copy
    - Track 1, Lesson 1 (Box 9)
    - Track 2, Lesson 2 (Box 9)
    - Track 1, Lesson 3 (Box 10)
    - Track 2, Lesson 4 (Box 10)
    - Track 1, Lesson 5 (Box 10)
    - Track 2, Lesson 6 (Box 10)
    - Track 1, Lesson 7 (Box 10)
    - Track 2, Lesson 8 (Box 10)
    - Track 1, Lesson 9 (Box 10)
    - Track 2, Lesson 10 (Box 10)
    - Track 1, Lesson 11 (Box 10)
    - Track 2, Lesson 12 (Box 10)
    - Track 1, Lesson 13 (Box 10)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-144
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2006-089
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, second-level, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of participants at Bad Boll institute, third-level, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RSVP slips for Bad Boll reunion, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letterhead, NDEA Institute for Advance Study (Box 1, Folder 12)